Viewers, whatever spirit that stand up against your career
your life,
your destiny,
your health,
your finances,
In the name of Jesus...
out!
Out!
Viewers all over the world, begin to command that
spirit that seems to stand against you,
that spirit that stands against your business.
That spirit that stands against your career.
Viewers all over the world, begin to order them (those spirits),
order them out of your life.
Order them out of your business.
Order them out of your future!
Order them out of your destiny!
Order them!
You demon...
familiar spirit...order them out in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus Name.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are
in every hidden place,
order the demons.
Order them out!
Order the familiar spirit!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers, it is time to establish your word,
what has been established in heaven, has been established.
I say you are delivered in the name of Jesus!
It is established the you have been delivered, in the name of Jesus!
It is established that you have been rescued!
You have been made free!
Say, I am free!
Say, "I am delivered in the name of Jesus!"
I am delivered!
I am free!
Rejoice!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua,
touch the screen by faith in Jesus Name.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip that you have watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV...changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.